JERRYEBIKARI NEEDAM

WEB DEVELOPER

ebikari.vercel.app

08102571705

jerryebikarineedam@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Web developer with a solid foundation built from years of working on personal projects and internships. I have experience using a wide variety of web development technology, ranging from regular frontend and backend languages, to cloud technologies like AWS for deployment, as well as task automation with Ansible and OS specific scripting tools.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer Intern

December 2023 - May 2024

AltSchool Africa

- Learn frontend and backend web development.
- Build frontend project.
- Build backend project.

Fullstack Developer

January 2022 - Present

- Learn to use web development and cloud technologies like React, Angular, Node.js, SpringBoot, AWS and more.
- Build portfolio projects.

Frontend Developer

November 2022 - April 2023

Haptle Technologies Limited

- Build responsive and elegant web UIs with bleeding-edge HTML/CSS specs, advanced JavaScript libraries and similar technologies.
- Design, develop, test, deploy, maintain and improve software applications.
- Manage individual project priorities, deadlines and deliverables.

EDUCATION

B.Eng Electrical/Electronic Engineering (First Class Honours)

2015 - 2021

Niger Delta University, Wilberforce Island, Bayelsa

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS, MUI
- JavaScript
- Angular
- React
- Node Js
- Express Js
- MongoDB
- Java
- MySQL
- Java Play
- PostgreSQL
- Spring Boot
 - g Boot Git